(Raj:)Zero women, that's my sweet spot.
(Penny:)Unless you're sleeping
with one of them,
(Penny:)seeing other people isn't a big deal.
(Raj:)But what if one of them asks me
what I was up to the night before
(Raj:)and I was with the other one?
Then, what, do I lie?
(Raj:)-Yes.
-Yes.
(Bernadette:)What do you mean, yes?
(Bernadette:)Were you seeing other women
when we started dating?
(Howard:)No. Were you seeing other men?
(Leonard:)No.
(Howard:)Were you seeing other men?
(Leonard:)Aren't you gonna ask me?
(Penny:)Come on, really?
(Leonard:)Thank you so much
for letting us pick your brain.
(Wil Wheaton:)Yeah, happy to help.
So, what's going on?
(Penny:)Well, I'm having an impossible time
getting my career off the ground,
(Penny:)and I got offered a role
in this crappy horror movie,
(Penny:)and I just don't know
if I should take it.
(Wil:)Well, I have certainly taken some
jobs that I've been embarrassed by.
(Penny:)I wouldn't exactly call
Star Trek embarrassing.